(Raj:)Hey, did I say
something to upset you?
(Howard:)No, I'm fine.
(Raj:)Really? Because usually
we walk side by side,
(Raj:)and I just went up
two flights of stairs
(Raj:)staring at your bottom.
(Howard:)Just drop it.
(Raj:)Okay, I think I see
what's happening here.
(Raj:)You're jealous of me.
(Howard:)Oh, please.
(Howard:)What could you possibly have
that I would be jealous of?
(Raj:)It's not what I have, it's how
many people I'm having it with.
(Penny:)Come on, Sheldon, we'll watch
Game of Thrones over here.
- Gladly.
LEONARD: - Oh, good, go.
(Leonard:)You know, it'll be nice
(Leonard:)to watch an episode
without someone saying,
"I read the books.
(Leonard:)Don't get too fond
of this character."
(Sheldon:)It's not always
because they die.
(Sheldon:)In one case, it's because
they've become involved
(Sheldon:)with underground tree people
from the dawn of time.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but I won't
say who it is.
It's Bran!
(Howard:)Wait, what is going on?
(Penny:)Leonard's being a jerk,
so we're gonna watch over here,
(Amy:)Do you guys want
to watch with us?
(Howard:)As long as I don't
have to watch with him.
(Raj:)Fine, I don't want to
watch with you either.
(Raj:)I'll go over here.
(Howard:)Why do you get to pick?
Okay, then you go there!
Don't tell me where to go!